so I feel distracted where's the time
the first step is putting yourself in
the common environment in other words no
matter how strong your resolve is to
calm your mind if you're in the middle
of sort of interaction engagement with
others with duties with noise visuals
you won't become so it's the wisdom lies
in preventing these things from
disturbing your peace so you want to see
it ahead before you are in such an
environment or if you already are you
want to see that it's been it's
necessary not just beneficial if you
want to calm your mind it is necessary
to step outside of that around even
temporarily so you want to calm down the
the circumstances around you isolate
yourself more from it then on the basis
of that you can start practicing
mindfulness and basically trying to
understand what makes calm mind calm
that's how you get knowledge and that's
how you can't be mind no no of course
not later on obviously if you if you are
when your mind is calm and when you're
stronger then you might end up in
circumstances that are not calm but you
remain unaffected but not until your
mind grew out of it imagine like I don't
know you you catch some infectious
disease and the first step is you get
out of that environment because you just
the environment is infecting you and
just causing you to be constantly sick
so then you have to spend a certain
amount of time in a non-infected
environment and then when you cure you
develop resistance then you can go back
if you have to to the interact
environment you won't be affected again
but it's the same it's the same if you
wanna calm down your mind and develop